[
    {
        "question": "考える",
        "answer": "かんがえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "増える",
        "answer": "ふえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "乗り物",
        "answer": "のりもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "見物",
        "answer": "けんぶつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "中学校",
        "answer": "ちゅうがっこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "気持ち",
        "answer": "きもち"
    },
    {
        "question": "翻訳",
        "answer": "ほんやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "急",
        "answer": "きゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "輸出",
        "answer": "ゆしゅつ・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "工業",
        "answer": "こうぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "進む",
        "answer": "すすむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "社会",
        "answer": "しゃかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "急行",
        "answer": "きゅうこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "受付",
        "answer": "うけつけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "火",
        "answer": "ひ"
    },
    {
        "question": "引っ越す",
        "answer": "ひっこす"
    },
    {
        "question": "負ける",
        "answer": "まける"
    },
    {
        "question": "落る",
        "answer": "おちる"
    },
    {
        "question": "数学",
        "answer": "すうがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "込む",
        "answer": "こむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "空気",
        "answer": "くうき"
    },
    {
        "question": "下る",
        "answer": "さがる"
    },
    {
        "question": "席",
        "answer": "せき"
    },
    {
        "question": "文学",
        "answer": "ぶんがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "小説",
        "answer": "しょうせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "笑う",
        "answer": "わらう"
    },
    {
        "question": "地理",
        "answer": "ちり"
    },
    {
        "question": "安心",
        "answer": "あんしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "心配",
        "answer": "しんぱい・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "坂",
        "answer": "さか"
    },
    {
        "question": "世界",
        "answer": "せかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "興味",
        "answer": "きょうみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "思い出す",
        "answer": "おもいだす"
    },
    {
        "question": "味噌",
        "answer": "みそ"
    },
    {
        "question": "別れる",
        "answer": "わかれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "味",
        "answer": "あじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "絹",
        "answer": "きぬ"
    },
    {
        "question": "治る",
        "answer": "なおる"
    },
    {
        "question": "投げる",
        "answer": "なげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "下宿",
        "answer": "げしゅく"
    },
    {
        "question": "復習",
        "answer": "ふくしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "祈る",
        "answer": "いのる"
    },
    {
        "question": "用事",
        "answer": "ようじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "注意",
        "answer": "ちゅうい"
    },
    {
        "question": "先輩",
        "answer": "せんぱい"
    },
    {
        "question": "お祝い",
        "answer": "おいわい"
    },
    {
        "question": "帰り",
        "answer": "かえり"
    },
    {
        "question": "割れる",
        "answer": "われる"
    },
    {
        "question": "気",
        "answer": "き"
    },
    {
        "question": "一生懸命",
        "answer": "いっしょうけんめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "参る",
        "answer": "まいる"
    },
    {
        "question": "珍しい",
        "answer": "めずらしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "品物",
        "answer": "しなもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "安全",
        "answer": "あんぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "戦争",
        "answer": "せんそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "塗る",
        "answer": "ぬる"
    },
    {
        "question": "明日",
        "answer": "あす"
    },
    {
        "question": "亡くなる",
        "answer": "なくなる"
    },
    {
        "question": "済む",
        "answer": "すむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "規則",
        "answer": "きそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "戻る",
        "answer": "もどる"
    },
    {
        "question": "お祭り",
        "answer": "おまつり"
    },
    {
        "question": "科学",
        "answer": "かがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "途中",
        "answer": "とちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "十分",
        "answer": "じゅうぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "歯医者",
        "answer": "はいしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "虫",
        "answer": "むし"
    },
    {
        "question": "堅/硬/固い",
        "answer": "かたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "草",
        "answer": "くさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "都",
        "answer": "と"
    },
    {
        "question": "島",
        "answer": "しま"
    },
    {
        "question": "見つかる",
        "answer": "みつかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "迎える",
        "answer": "むかえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "出席",
        "answer": "しゅっせき・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "昼休み",
        "answer": "ひるやすみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "鏡",
        "answer": "かがみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "始める",
        "answer": "はじめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "退院",
        "answer": "たいいん・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "準備",
        "answer": "じゅんび・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "お土産",
        "answer": "おみやげ"
    },
    {
        "question": "子",
        "answer": "こ"
    },
    {
        "question": "森",
        "answer": "もり"
    },
    {
        "question": "謝る",
        "answer": "あやまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "店員",
        "answer": "てんいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "掛ける",
        "answer": "かける"
    },
    {
        "question": "暮れる",
        "answer": "くれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "泥棒",
        "answer": "どろぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "出発",
        "answer": "しゅっぱつ・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "盛ん",
        "answer": "さかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "必要",
        "answer": "ひつよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "釣る",
        "answer": "つる"
    },
    {
        "question": "君",
        "answer": "きみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "柔らかい",
        "answer": "やわらかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "特別",
        "answer": "とくべつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "僕",
        "answer": "ぼく"
    },
    {
        "question": "下りる",
        "answer": "おりる"
    },
    {
        "question": "案内",
        "answer": "あんない・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "飾る",
        "answer": "かざる"
    },
    {
        "question": "付く",
        "answer": "つく"
    },
    {
        "question": "女性",
        "answer": "じょせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "沸く",
        "answer": "わく"
    },
    {
        "question": "間に合う",
        "answer": "まにあう"
    },
    {
        "question": "踏む",
        "answer": "ふむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "予定",
        "answer": "よてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "さ来月",
        "answer": "さらいげつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "隅",
        "answer": "すみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "市",
        "answer": "し"
    },
    {
        "question": "課長",
        "answer": "かちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "木綿",
        "answer": "もめん"
    },
    {
        "question": "恥ずかしい",
        "answer": "はずかしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "割合",
        "answer": "わりあい"
    },
    {
        "question": "最近",
        "answer": "さいきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "文化",
        "answer": "ぶんか"
    },
    {
        "question": "特急",
        "answer": "とっきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "指輪",
        "answer": "ゆびわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "相談",
        "answer": "そうだん・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "時代",
        "answer": "じだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "見つける",
        "answer": "みつける"
    },
    {
        "question": "柔道",
        "answer": "じゅうどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "湖",
        "answer": "みずうみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "楽む",
        "answer": "たのしむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "答",
        "answer": "こたえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "入院",
        "answer": "にゅういん・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "彼ら",
        "answer": "かれら"
    },
    {
        "question": "大事",
        "answer": "だいじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "集める",
        "answer": "あつめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "生産",
        "answer": "せいさん・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "美しい",
        "answer": "うつくしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "法律",
        "answer": "ほうりつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "郊外",
        "answer": "こうがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "建てる",
        "answer": "たてる"
    },
    {
        "question": "降り出す",
        "answer": "ふりだす"
    },
    {
        "question": "失敗",
        "answer": "しっぱい"
    },
    {
        "question": "無くなる",
        "answer": "なくなる"
    },
    {
        "question": "連れる",
        "answer": "つれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "遅れる",
        "answer": "おくれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "お見舞い",
        "answer": "おみまい"
    },
    {
        "question": "丁寧",
        "answer": "ていねい"
    },
    {
        "question": "変わる",
        "answer": "かわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "招待",
        "answer": "しょうたい・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "高等学校",
        "answer": "こうとうがっこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "終わり",
        "answer": "おわり"
    },
    {
        "question": "点",
        "answer": "てん"
    },
    {
        "question": "寄る",
        "answer": "よる"
    },
    {
        "question": "食事",
        "answer": "しょくじ・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "教育",
        "answer": "きょういく"
    },
    {
        "question": "祖母",
        "answer": "そぼ"
    },
    {
        "question": "電報",
        "answer": "でんぽう"
    },
    {
        "question": "花見",
        "answer": "はなみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "政治",
        "answer": "せいじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "打つ",
        "answer": "うつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "両方",
        "answer": "りょうほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "毛",
        "answer": "け"
    },
    {
        "question": "喜ぶ",
        "answer": "よろこぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "引き出し",
        "answer": "ひきだし"
    },
    {
        "question": "痩せる",
        "answer": "やせる"
    },
    {
        "question": "受ける",
        "answer": "うける"
    },
    {
        "question": "決して",
        "answer": "けっして"
    },
    {
        "question": "皆",
        "answer": "みな"
    },
    {
        "question": "季節",
        "answer": "きせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "火事",
        "answer": "かじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "贈り物",
        "answer": "おくりもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "飛行場",
        "answer": "ひこうじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "故障",
        "answer": "こしょう・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "予習",
        "answer": "よしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "調べる",
        "answer": "しらべる"
    },
    {
        "question": "注射",
        "answer": "ちゅうしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "卒業",
        "answer": "そつぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "予約",
        "answer": "よやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "一度",
        "answer": "いちど"
    },
    {
        "question": "星",
        "answer": "ほし"
    },
    {
        "question": "日記",
        "answer": "にっき"
    },
    {
        "question": "適当",
        "answer": "てきとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "景色",
        "answer": "けしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "連絡",
        "answer": "れんらく"
    },
    {
        "question": "写す",
        "answer": "うつす"
    },
    {
        "question": "雲",
        "answer": "くも"
    },
    {
        "question": "押し入れ",
        "answer": "おしいれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "確か",
        "answer": "たしか"
    },
    {
        "question": "小鳥",
        "answer": "ことり"
    },
    {
        "question": "交通",
        "answer": "こうつう"
    },
    {
        "question": "台風",
        "answer": "たいふう"
    },
    {
        "question": "教会",
        "answer": "きょうかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "引き出す",
        "answer": "ひきだす"
    },
    {
        "question": "倒れる",
        "answer": "たおれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "承知",
        "answer": "しょうち・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "別",
        "answer": "べつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "娘",
        "answer": "むすめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "複雑",
        "answer": "ふくざつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "仕方",
        "answer": "しかた"
    },
    {
        "question": "以内",
        "answer": "いない"
    },
    {
        "question": "放送",
        "answer": "ほうそう・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "片付ける",
        "answer": "かたづける"
    },
    {
        "question": "心",
        "answer": "こころ"
    },
    {
        "question": "泣く",
        "answer": "なく"
    },
    {
        "question": "間",
        "answer": "あいだ"
    },
    {
        "question": "空く",
        "answer": "あく"
    },
    {
        "question": "凄い",
        "answer": "すごい"
    },
    {
        "question": "舟",
        "answer": "ふね"
    },
    {
        "question": "普通",
        "answer": "ふつう"
    },
    {
        "question": "動物園",
        "answer": "どうぶつえん"
    },
    {
        "question": "留守",
        "answer": "るす"
    },
    {
        "question": "訳",
        "answer": "わけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "久しぶり",
        "answer": "ひさしぶり"
    },
    {
        "question": "残る",
        "answer": "のこる"
    },
    {
        "question": "看護婦",
        "answer": "かんごふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "続く",
        "answer": "つづく"
    },
    {
        "question": "貿易",
        "answer": "ぼうえき"
    },
    {
        "question": "研究室",
        "answer": "けんきゅうしつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "焼ける",
        "answer": "やける"
    },
    {
        "question": "真中",
        "answer": "まんなか"
    },
    {
        "question": "以外",
        "answer": "いがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "浅い",
        "answer": "あさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "盗む",
        "answer": "ぬすむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "約束",
        "answer": "やくそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "周り",
        "answer": "まわり"
    },
    {
        "question": "文法",
        "answer": "ぶんぽう"
    },
    {
        "question": "噛む",
        "answer": "かむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "遠慮",
        "answer": "えんりょ・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "赤ん坊",
        "answer": "あかんぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "寝坊",
        "answer": "ねぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "壁",
        "answer": "かべ"
    },
    {
        "question": "講義",
        "answer": "こうぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "妻",
        "answer": "つま"
    },
    {
        "question": "お・金持ち",
        "answer": "かねもち/おかねもち"
    },
    {
        "question": "残念",
        "answer": "ざんねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "変える",
        "answer": "かえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "育てる",
        "answer": "そだてる"
    },
    {
        "question": "意見",
        "answer": "いけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "食料品",
        "answer": "しょくりょうひん"
    },
    {
        "question": "将来",
        "answer": "しょうらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "形",
        "answer": "かたち"
    },
    {
        "question": "立てる",
        "answer": "たてる"
    },
    {
        "question": "警察",
        "answer": "けいさつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "眠い",
        "answer": "ねむい"
    },
    {
        "question": "沸かす",
        "answer": "わかす"
    },
    {
        "question": "大学生",
        "answer": "だいがくせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "具合",
        "answer": "ぐあい"
    },
    {
        "question": "代わり",
        "answer": "かわり"
    },
    {
        "question": "市民",
        "answer": "しみん"
    },
    {
        "question": "回る",
        "answer": "まわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "冷える",
        "answer": "ひえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "思う",
        "answer": "おもう"
    },
    {
        "question": "細かい",
        "answer": "こまかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "研究",
        "answer": "けんきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "拾う",
        "answer": "ひろう"
    },
    {
        "question": "畳",
        "answer": "たたみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "腕",
        "answer": "うで"
    },
    {
        "question": "払う",
        "answer": "はらう"
    },
    {
        "question": "力",
        "answer": "ちから"
    },
    {
        "question": "道具",
        "answer": "どうぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "港",
        "answer": "みなと"
    },
    {
        "question": "息子",
        "answer": "むすこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "汚れる",
        "answer": "よごれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "悲しい",
        "answer": "かなしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "捕まえる",
        "answer": "つかまえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "彼女",
        "answer": "かのじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "最後",
        "answer": "さいご"
    },
    {
        "question": "紹介",
        "answer": "しょうかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "驚く",
        "answer": "おどろく"
    },
    {
        "question": "決る",
        "answer": "きまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "申す",
        "answer": "もうす"
    },
    {
        "question": "怒る",
        "answer": "おこる"
    },
    {
        "question": "乗り換える",
        "answer": "のりかえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "大体",
        "answer": "だいたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "石",
        "answer": "いし"
    },
    {
        "question": "生活",
        "answer": "せいかつ・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "関係",
        "answer": "かんけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "夢",
        "answer": "ゆめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "米",
        "answer": "こめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "眠る",
        "answer": "ねむる"
    },
    {
        "question": "駐車場",
        "answer": "ちゅうしゃじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "召し上がる",
        "answer": "めしあがる"
    },
    {
        "question": "会場",
        "answer": "かいじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "枝",
        "answer": "えだ"
    },
    {
        "question": "歴史",
        "answer": "れきし"
    },
    {
        "question": "折る",
        "answer": "おる"
    },
    {
        "question": "泳ぎ方",
        "answer": "およぎかた"
    },
    {
        "question": "布団",
        "answer": "ふとん"
    },
    {
        "question": "最初",
        "answer": "さいしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "怖い",
        "answer": "こわい"
    },
    {
        "question": "展覧会",
        "answer": "てんらんかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "彼",
        "answer": "かれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "美術館",
        "answer": "びじゅつかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "裏",
        "answer": "うら"
    },
    {
        "question": "人口",
        "answer": "じんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "止める",
        "answer": "とめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "運動",
        "answer": "うんどう・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "血",
        "answer": "ち"
    },
    {
        "question": "電灯",
        "answer": "でんとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "空港",
        "answer": "くうこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "過ぎる",
        "answer": "すぎる"
    },
    {
        "question": "昼間",
        "answer": "ひるま"
    },
    {
        "question": "親切",
        "answer": "しんせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "髪",
        "answer": "かみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "用意",
        "answer": "ようい"
    },
    {
        "question": "開く",
        "answer": "ひらく"
    },
    {
        "question": "返事",
        "answer": "へんじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "用",
        "answer": "よう"
    },
    {
        "question": "技術",
        "answer": "ぎじゅつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "工場",
        "answer": "こうじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "糸",
        "answer": "いと"
    },
    {
        "question": "起す",
        "answer": "おこす"
    },
    {
        "question": "逃げる",
        "answer": "にげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "利用",
        "answer": "りよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "届ける",
        "answer": "とどける"
    },
    {
        "question": "通る",
        "answer": "とおる"
    },
    {
        "question": "住所",
        "answer": "じゅうしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "経済",
        "answer": "けいざい"
    },
    {
        "question": "直る",
        "answer": "なおる"
    },
    {
        "question": "さ来週",
        "answer": "さらいしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "入学",
        "answer": "にゅうがく・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "折れる",
        "answer": "おれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "不便",
        "answer": "ふべん"
    },
    {
        "question": "落す",
        "answer": "おとす"
    },
    {
        "question": "運ぶ",
        "answer": "はこぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "申し上げる",
        "answer": "もうしあげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "汽車",
        "answer": "きしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "小学校",
        "answer": "しょうがっこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "止む",
        "answer": "やむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "役に立つ",
        "answer": "やくにたつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "背中",
        "answer": "せなか"
    },
    {
        "question": "倍",
        "answer": "ばい"
    },
    {
        "question": "遊び",
        "answer": "あそび"
    },
    {
        "question": "苦い",
        "answer": "にがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "決める",
        "answer": "きめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "気分",
        "answer": "きぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "尋ねる",
        "answer": "たずねる"
    },
    {
        "question": "壊れる",
        "answer": "こわれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "滑る",
        "answer": "すべる"
    },
    {
        "question": "伝える",
        "answer": "つたえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "ご存じ",
        "answer": "ごぞんじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "お宅",
        "answer": "おたく"
    },
    {
        "question": "お嬢さん",
        "answer": "おじょうさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "億",
        "answer": "おく"
    },
    {
        "question": "海岸",
        "answer": "かいがん"
    },
    {
        "question": "手袋",
        "answer": "てぶくろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "漫画",
        "answer": "まんが"
    },
    {
        "question": "動く",
        "answer": "うごく"
    },
    {
        "question": "着物",
        "answer": "きもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "医学",
        "answer": "いがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "西洋",
        "answer": "せいよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "字",
        "answer": "じ"
    },
    {
        "question": "上る",
        "answer": "あがる"
    },
    {
        "question": "下げる",
        "answer": "さげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "正しい",
        "answer": "ただしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "経験",
        "answer": "けいけん・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "比べる",
        "answer": "くらべる"
    },
    {
        "question": "男性",
        "answer": "だんせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "表",
        "answer": "おもて"
    },
    {
        "question": "校長",
        "answer": "こうちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "会議",
        "answer": "かいぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "触る",
        "answer": "さわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "送る",
        "answer": "おくる"
    },
    {
        "question": "大分",
        "answer": "だいぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "線",
        "answer": "せん"
    },
    {
        "question": "行う",
        "answer": "おこなう"
    },
    {
        "question": "支度",
        "answer": "したく・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "反対",
        "answer": "はんたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "輸入",
        "answer": "ゆにゅう・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "壊す",
        "answer": "こわす"
    },
    {
        "question": "熱",
        "answer": "ねつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "会議室",
        "answer": "かいぎしつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "屋上",
        "answer": "おくじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "為",
        "answer": "ため"
    },
    {
        "question": "棚",
        "answer": "たな"
    },
    {
        "question": "説明",
        "answer": "せつめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "急ぐ",
        "answer": "いそぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "捨てる",
        "answer": "すてる"
    },
    {
        "question": "足りる",
        "answer": "たりる"
    },
    {
        "question": "選ぶ",
        "answer": "えらぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "移る",
        "answer": "うつる"
    },
    {
        "question": "探す",
        "answer": "さがす"
    },
    {
        "question": "発音",
        "answer": "はつおん"
    },
    {
        "question": "試合",
        "answer": "しあい"
    },
    {
        "question": "今度",
        "answer": "こんど"
    },
    {
        "question": "取り替える",
        "answer": "とりかえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "原因",
        "answer": "げんいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "公務員",
        "answer": "こうむいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "親",
        "answer": "おや"
    },
    {
        "question": "鳴る",
        "answer": "なる"
    },
    {
        "question": "焼く",
        "answer": "やく"
    },
    {
        "question": "機会",
        "answer": "きかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "厳しい",
        "answer": "きびしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "水道",
        "answer": "すいどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "客",
        "answer": "きゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "訪ねる",
        "answer": "たずねる"
    },
    {
        "question": "運転",
        "answer": "うんてん・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "辞典",
        "answer": "じてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "産業",
        "answer": "さんぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "似る",
        "answer": "にる"
    },
    {
        "question": "特に",
        "answer": "とくに"
    },
    {
        "question": "旅館",
        "answer": "りょかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "計画",
        "answer": "けいかく・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "以下",
        "answer": "いか"
    },
    {
        "question": "田舎",
        "answer": "いなか"
    },
    {
        "question": "寺",
        "answer": "てら"
    },
    {
        "question": "楽しみ",
        "answer": "たのしみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "続ける",
        "answer": "つづける"
    },
    {
        "question": "会話",
        "answer": "かいわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "冷房",
        "answer": "れいぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "致す",
        "answer": "いたす"
    },
    {
        "question": "湯",
        "answer": "ゆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "番組",
        "answer": "ばんぐみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "差し上げる",
        "answer": "さしあげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "音",
        "answer": "おと"
    },
    {
        "question": "揺れる",
        "answer": "ゆれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "事務所",
        "answer": "じむしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "無理",
        "answer": "むり"
    },
    {
        "question": "新聞社",
        "answer": "しんぶんしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "以上",
        "answer": "いじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "踊り",
        "answer": "おどり"
    },
    {
        "question": "通う",
        "answer": "かよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "非常に",
        "answer": "ひじょうに"
    },
    {
        "question": "深い",
        "answer": "ふかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "例えば",
        "answer": "たとえば"
    },
    {
        "question": "事故",
        "answer": "じこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "消しゴム",
        "answer": "けしゴム"
    },
    {
        "question": "騒ぐ",
        "answer": "さわぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "見える",
        "answer": "みえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "手伝う",
        "answer": "てつだう"
    },
    {
        "question": "家内",
        "answer": "かない"
    },
    {
        "question": "売り場",
        "answer": "うりば"
    },
    {
        "question": "間違える",
        "answer": "まちがえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "変",
        "answer": "へん"
    },
    {
        "question": "理由",
        "answer": "りゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "趣味",
        "answer": "しゅみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "優しい",
        "answer": "やさしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "今夜",
        "answer": "こんや"
    },
    {
        "question": "昔",
        "answer": "むかし"
    },
    {
        "question": "習慣",
        "answer": "しゅうかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "生きる",
        "answer": "いきる"
    },
    {
        "question": "運転手",
        "answer": "うんてんしゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "祖父",
        "answer": "そふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "太る",
        "answer": "ふとる"
    },
    {
        "question": "天気予報",
        "answer": "てんきよほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "二階建て",
        "answer": "にかいだて"
    },
    {
        "question": "包む",
        "answer": "つつむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "夫",
        "answer": "おっと"
    },
    {
        "question": "水泳",
        "answer": "すいえい"
    },
    {
        "question": "御主人",
        "answer": "ごしゅじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "直す",
        "answer": "なおす"
    },
    {
        "question": "漬ける",
        "answer": "つける"
    },
    {
        "question": "聞こえる",
        "answer": "きこえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "競争",
        "answer": "きょうそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "地震",
        "answer": "じしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "部長",
        "answer": "ぶちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "都合",
        "answer": "つごう"
    },
    {
        "question": "乾く",
        "answer": "かわく"
    },
    {
        "question": "植える",
        "answer": "うえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "暖房",
        "answer": "だんぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "光",
        "answer": "ひかり"
    },
    {
        "question": "世話",
        "answer": "せわ・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "高校生",
        "answer": "こうこうせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "林",
        "answer": "はやし"
    },
    {
        "question": "忘れ物",
        "answer": "わすれもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "遠く",
        "answer": "とおく"
    },
    {
        "question": "知らせる",
        "answer": "しらせる"
    },
    {
        "question": "場合",
        "answer": "ばあい"
    },
    {
        "question": "高校",
        "answer": "こうこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "講堂",
        "answer": "こうどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "近所",
        "answer": "きんじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "日",
        "answer": "ひ"
    },
    {
        "question": "危険",
        "answer": "きけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "自由",
        "answer": "じゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "場所",
        "answer": "ばしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "砂",
        "answer": "すな"
    },
    {
        "question": "合う",
        "answer": "あう"
    },
    {
        "question": "向かう",
        "answer": "むかう"
    },
    {
        "question": "国際",
        "answer": "こくさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "葉",
        "answer": "は"
    },
    {
        "question": "集る",
        "answer": "あつまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "下着",
        "answer": "したぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "指",
        "answer": "ゆび"
    },
    {
        "question": "首",
        "answer": "くび"
    },
    {
        "question": "人形",
        "answer": "にんぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "寂しい",
        "answer": "さびしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "光る",
        "answer": "ひかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "試験",
        "answer": "しけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "踊る",
        "answer": "おどる"
    },
    {
        "question": "中々",
        "answer": "なかなか"
    },
    {
        "question": "足す",
        "answer": "たす"
    },
    {
        "question": "勝つ",
        "answer": "かつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "拝見",
        "answer": "はいけん・する"
    },
    {
        "question": "お礼",
        "answer": "おれい"
    },
    {
        "question": "神社",
        "answer": "じんじゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "簡単",
        "answer": "かんたん"
    },
    {
        "question": "泊まる",
        "answer": "とまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "慣れる",
        "answer": "なれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "必ず",
        "answer": "かならず"
    },
    {
        "question": "社長",
        "answer": "しゃちょう"
    }
]